<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content on CyberTractor Challenge</title>
    <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content on CyberTractor Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:15:59 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship Drive</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/sponsor_drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:15:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/sponsor_drive/</guid>
      <description>Update! Click HERE to submit your official offer of sponsorship for the 2025 CyberTractor Challenge&#xA;Dear Visionaries, Innovators, and those linked to the land,&#xA;I am excited to announce that we are gearing up for the 4th Annual CyberTractor Challenge, set for June 16-20, 2025, near the dynamic campus of Iowa State University, and it&amp;rsquo;s that time where we must start on the process of finding sponsors! With preparations already underway from curriculum planning by our esteemed Board of Directors to student recruitment — we are on the threshold of bringing another groundbreaking event to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apply to the 2025 CyberTractor Challenge!</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:37:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/apply/</guid>
      <description>Happy Holidays Cybersecurity Enthusiasts and Ag-Tech Innovators!&#xA;Grab your overalls, throw on some boots, and get ready for the 2025 CyberTractor Challenge! Join us on June 15-20, 2025 in the heartland of the USA to learn from industry leaders, academic instructors, experts, and our generous sponsors about the exciting field of agriculture cybersecurity! It&amp;rsquo;s the fourth year of our event, SECOND year as a 501c3 Non-Profit, and we’re bigger and better than ever!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you to our 2024 CyberTractor Challenge Sponsors!</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/thank_you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 11:51:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/thank_you/</guid>
      <description>We would like to extend our heartfelt gratitude to our 2024 CyberTractor Challenge sponsors. Our sponsors share our commitment to fostering a more secure agricultural industry by educating the next generation of agricultural &amp;amp; cybersecurity professionals with the knowledge and skills necessary to tackle the unique cybersecurity challenges facing modern farming.&#xA;Our Sponsors This year, we are proud to partner with the following sponsors whose support and commitment to our cause helps us achieve our goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting_up</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/starting_up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:00:37 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/starting_up/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the CyberTractor Challenge! This page is under construction.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
