<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content on CyberTractor Challenge</title>
    <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content on CyberTractor Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:37:29 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apply to the 2024 CyberTractor Challenge!</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:37:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/apply/</guid>
      <description>Happy Leap-Year Cybersecurity Enthusiasts and Ag-Tech Innovators!&#xA;CyberTractor Challenge is approaching rapidly, taking place June 10-14 2024 right here in the heartland of the USA! We&amp;rsquo;ve evolved from a single-brand initiative to an independent 501c3 with a broader venture under our shiny new non-profit status. This means more perspectives, more cool tech, and yes, more tractors of more colors! Our event puts you in the room with some of the experts who built the very systems on which you will be training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship Drive</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/sponsor_drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 15:15:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/sponsor_drive/</guid>
      <description>Update! Click HERE to submit your official offer of sponsorship for the 2024 CyberTractor Challenge&#xA;Dear Visionaries, Innovators, and those linked to the land,&#xA;I am excited to announce that we are gearing up for the 3rd Annual CyberTractor Challenge, set for June 10-14, 2024, near the dynamic campus of Iowa State University, and it&amp;rsquo;s that time where we must start on the process of finding sponsors! With preparations already underway from curriculum planning by our esteemed Board of Directors to student recruitment — we are on the threshold of bringing another groundbreaking event to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting_up</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/starting_up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:00:37 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/starting_up/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the CyberTractor Challenge! This page is under construction.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
