<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CyberTractor Challenge</title>
    <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CyberTractor Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:01:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cybertractorchallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2025_selection</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/2025_selection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/2025_selection/</guid>
      <description>2025 CyberTractor Challenge Student Selections Completed! The CyberTractor Challenge team is excited to announce that student selections for the 2025 CyberTractor Challenge have been completed! We are thrilled to welcome a diverse group of talented students from across the country who will be joining us in June for this unique opportunity to learn, collaborate, and innovate in the field of agriculture cybersecurity. The CyberTractor Challenge exists to develop talent and build community to solve hard and interesting problems related to the security of modern connected agricultural equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor Packages</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/static/sponsor_packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:00:01 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/static/sponsor_packages/</guid>
      <description>Dear Potential Sponsor: CyberTractor Challenge appreciates your interest in sponsoring our 3rd Annual event being held June 16-20, 2025, just 45 minutes north of the capitol of Iowa at the home of the Iowa State University Cyclones. As you read this, trainers are being approached by the Board of Directors to set classes, venue arrangements are being made, infrastructure is being created, recruiting of student applicants is underway, and more is in progress to bring this exciting event to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship Drive</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/sponsor_drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:15:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/sponsor_drive/</guid>
      <description>Update! Click HERE to submit your official offer of sponsorship for the 2025 CyberTractor Challenge&#xA;Dear Visionaries, Innovators, and those linked to the land,&#xA;I am excited to announce that we are gearing up for the 4th Annual CyberTractor Challenge, set for June 16-20, 2025, near the dynamic campus of Iowa State University, and it&amp;rsquo;s that time where we must start on the process of finding sponsors! With preparations already underway from curriculum planning by our esteemed Board of Directors to student recruitment — we are on the threshold of bringing another groundbreaking event to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apply</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/static/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 10:43:25 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/static/apply/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apply to the 2025 CyberTractor Challenge!</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 10:37:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/apply/</guid>
      <description>Happy Holidays Cybersecurity Enthusiasts and Ag-Tech Innovators!&#xA;Grab your overalls, throw on some boots, and get ready for the 2025 CyberTractor Challenge! Join us on June 15-20, 2025 in the heartland of the USA to learn from industry leaders, academic instructors, experts, and our generous sponsors about the exciting field of agriculture cybersecurity! It&amp;rsquo;s the fourth year of our event, SECOND year as a 501c3 Non-Profit, and we’re bigger and better than ever!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you to our 2024 CyberTractor Challenge Sponsors!</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/thank_you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 11:51:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/thank_you/</guid>
      <description>We would like to extend our heartfelt gratitude to our 2024 CyberTractor Challenge sponsors. Our sponsors share our commitment to fostering a more secure agricultural industry by educating the next generation of agricultural &amp;amp; cybersecurity professionals with the knowledge and skills necessary to tackle the unique cybersecurity challenges facing modern farming.&#xA;Our Sponsors This year, we are proud to partner with the following sponsors whose support and commitment to our cause helps us achieve our goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other Challenges</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/static/other_challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:39:17 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/static/other_challenges/</guid>
      <description>This page under construction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting_up</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/starting_up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:00:37 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/post/starting_up/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the CyberTractor Challenge! This page is under construction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The CyberTractor Challenge (English: Tractor Hacking) was started by John Deere in 2022 as a sister event to the more established CyberTruck and CyberAuto challenges, focusing on the cybersecurity of their modern connected Agricultural fleet by bringing college and university students to a real farm in Iowa to get hands on experience with real equipment and real cybersecurity + engineering professionals. As the seeds of CyberTractor sprouted, the goals and scope for this &amp;ldquo;challenge&amp;rdquo; have pivoted from focusing on solely the iconic Green and Yellow equipment to include industry peers of all colors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cybertractorchallenge.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in learning more about the CyberTractor Challenge, please fill out this form to notify us and a member of our team will be in contact.&#xA;Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
